https://www.yarnbarn-ks.com/privacy.asp

Privacy Policy Statement
You are on the website of The Yarn Barn of Kansas, inc..
Our postal address is
930 Massachusetts St
Lawrence, KS 66044
We can be reached via email at info@yarnbarn-ks.com or you can reach us by telephone at 785-842-4333.
Yarn Barn respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect and maintain personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell, trade, or distribute your personally identifiable information, including your physical or email address, or telephone number, to anyone. Personally identifiable information obtained will only be used to process the order of intent. If you place an order we will also collect your name, mailing address, and email address.
We never rent, sell, trade, or otherwise provide your name or other personal information to other individuals or businesses unless required to do so to comply with a request from governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.
We use your telephone number only if we have questions about your order.
If you supply us with your address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above, or emailing us at the above address.
For your security, when we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server that has an SSL certificate using at least 128-bit encryption. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
If you have any questions or concerns, please contact us.
Yarn Barn accepts Mastercard, Visa, Discover, and Yarn Barn gift certificates on this website.
Visit our retail store at 930 Massachusetts St., Monday-Saturday 10:00-5:00 and Sunday 1:00-4:00.
Mail order telephone answered Monday-Friday, 9:00-5:00, Saturday, 9:00-1:30.  All times Central.
